<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <channel>
    <title>KamboyDev&#39;s Cool Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KamboyDev&#39;s Cool Website</description>
    
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:01:54 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is the Theme for the Website?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/what-is-the-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:01:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/what-is-the-theme/</guid>
      <description>The theme I&amp;rsquo;m using for the website is Everforest Dark, which is a Neovim theme.
Not much else to say. Have a good day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed About Link</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/fixed-about-link/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/fixed-about-link/</guid>
      <description>You should be able to click the About link now.
Also, I updated the site a bit more to remove placeholder text from the theme I used for the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 20:07:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/en/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Website! I will be posting about my projects, and other things. This first post will serve as a test of how markdown is displayed on the website (so I can fix CSS issues).
Second Heading Third Fourth Some style testing.
bro notch needs to get on this asap how am i supposed to play my infinite lego game
Some guy in the Modern Beta SMP Discord Server First item Second item Third item First item Second item Third item code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a teenage furry trying to be a programmer for video games.
I am a Sophomore, and I&amp;rsquo;m hoping I will be able to get out of High School without dropping out.
My favorite programming fonts Cascadia Code: A pretty good ligatured font for a not so great company. Mononoki: The only font that I have seen that looks smooth with bad font rendering from the not so great company above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
